Guide to the Wallace Notestein Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1899-1969; Series I; (11 boxes)
  - Emerson, William R., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Emmison, F. G., 1950-1957 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Engle, J. R., undated (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Evans, Mary, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Esdaile, Edmund, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Evans, Paul D., undated (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Everitt, Alan M., 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Fairfield, Letitia, undated (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Farnham, Edith, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Farnam, Thomas W., 1929-1932 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Farrand, Livingston, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Farrand, Max, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Ferguson, A. S., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Finch, Katherine, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Firth, C. H., 1907-1936, undated (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Fisher, George S., 1900-1902 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Fitz, Reginald, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Flaterie, Irene Phillips, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Flint, Richard Foster, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Forbes, Anthony H., 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Ford, Guy Stanton, 1913-1945 (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Ford, Worthington C., 1912-1914 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Fordyce, C. J., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Fosdick, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Foster, Dick and Elizabeth, 1947-1962, 1967 undated (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Foster, Dorothy, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Foster, Elizabeth Vincent, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan, 1934-1939 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Frame, John Davidson, 1900-1930 (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Frame, Murray S., undated (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - France, R. Sharpe, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1931-1936 (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - Fraser, Ian H. C., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - French, Robert, 1930-1943 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Friedlaender, Marc, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - Furniss, Edgar S., 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Gadney, H. G., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - Gage, Harry M., 1900-1958, undated (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - Galbraith, Vivian and Mrs., 1940-1954, undated (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - Gardner, James P., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - Garfield, H. A., 1908 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - Garver, M. S., 1905-1913, undated (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - Garretson, N. P., 1902-1912 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Gaskill, Gussie, undated (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Gerould, James Thayer, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - Geyl, Pieter, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  - Gibson, W. H., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Gimble, Ian, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Gleed, Charles S., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Glass, Meta, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - Gooch, G. P., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Goodfellow, Ernest W., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Gordon, Mrs. G. S., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Gottschalk, Louis R., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Grant, Isabel F., 1909 (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Grant, W. L., 1909-1912 (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Gras, N. S. B., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Graves, Henry S., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Graves, Mortimer, 1930-1946 (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Gray, Howard, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Gray, Margaret, 1912, undated (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Greaves, R. W., 1957 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Greene, Wilfred, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Greenough, William C., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Greig, Alison L., 1942, undated (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Gresswell, E. A., 1931 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Gretton, Mary S., 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Grey, Glen W., 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Grigg, P. J., 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Gross, Charles, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Grove, Clyde L., 1935 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Guerlac, Helen F., undated (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Gurney, J. H., 1912 (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Hackel, Anna, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Hackett, Francis, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Hadley, Helen, 1932-1939, undated (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Hadley, Morris, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Hagen, Beulah, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Haight, Gordon S., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Hales, Edward, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Hall, C. H., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Hall, Hubert, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Hamilton, George L. and Anita, 1928-1939 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Hamilton, Hamish, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Haring, C. H., 1931 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Harley, Hugh, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Harper, Isabel, 1928-1963, undated (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Harris, H. F., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Harris, R. W., 1930 (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Harsch, Joseph C., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Haskins, Charles H., 1916-1928 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Hassall, W. O., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Hawkin, T., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Hayes, Carlton J. H., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Hayes, G. H., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Hecht, Jean, undated (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Heiselmoyer Allen and Helen, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - Hele, T. S., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - Hemphill, Esther, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Hemphill, Wayne, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Hendrickson, Lincoln, undated (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Henning, Basil, 1938-1962, undated (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - Henning, Julia, undated (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Hersey, John, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - Hetherington, Hector, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Hexter, J. H., 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Heywood, Eileen (Mrs. Oliver), 1957 (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - Hicks, J. D., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Highham, C. S. S., 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Higham, F., undated (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Hill, Christopher, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Hilles, Frederick W., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Hillhouse, James T., undated (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Hillyer, R., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - Hinchman, Walter J., 1927 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Hinton, William, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Herbert, Phoebe, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Hodder, Frank H., 1909-1911 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - Hodder, Elizabeth, undated (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Hodgman, Corsly, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Holden, Reuben, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - Holdsworth, W., undated (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - Holman, J. C., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Holt, Ann, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Hotchkiss, Betty W., 1938-1950 (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - Hotchkiss, Joseph, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - Howard, Christopher, 1940-1948 (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Howard, G. Wren, 1938-1965 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Howard, Robert H., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Howe, Quincy, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Howland, C. (?), 1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Hudson, G. F., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - Hull, Charles and Mary, 1928-1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - Hulme, Harold, 1929-1946 (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - Humphreys, Humphrey, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 381A)
  - Humphreys, John A., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - Hunter, Richard, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - Hurstfield, Joel, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - Huxley, Ottlie, undated (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - Ingham, Alfred M., undated (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - Jacob, E. F., 1930 (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - James, Francis J., 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - Jameson, J. Franklin, 1907-1932 (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - Jenkinson, Frances, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Jervoise, F. H. T., 1936-1955 (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Johnson, Allen, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Johnson, Charles, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - Johnson, H. C., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - Johnson, K. R., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Johnson, William S., 1905-1929, undated (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Johnston, George P., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Johnston, J. B., 1914-1928 (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - Jones, Guernsey, undated (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Jones, Mariel, 1942-1950, undated (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - Jones, Tessie, 1915-1928 (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - Jordan, H. Donald, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - Jordan, W. K., 1947-1964 (Box 5, Folder 403)
  - Judson, Margaret, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 404)
  - Kades, Charles, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 405)
  - Kagin, Edwin, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 406)
  - Keder, Mary (Mrs. J. B.), 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 407)
  - Kenefick, Jame G., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1928-1933 (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - Keppel, F., 1918-1938 (Box 5, Folder 410)
  - Kerr, Chester B., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - Kerr, Philip, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 412)
  - Kiaffer, Fern, undated (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - Kilbourn, William M., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 414)
  - Kirchwey, George, undated (Box 5, Folder 415)
  - Klein, E. W., 1902 (Box 5, Folder 416)
  - Knappen, Marshall, 1928-1947 (Box 5, Folder 417)
  - Krapp, Elaine R., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 418)
  - Kraushaar, Otto F., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 419)
  - Krey, A. C., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 420)
  - Krock, Arthur, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 421)
  - Kukiel, M., 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 422)
  - Labaree, Leonard W., 1940-1947 (Box 5, Folder 423)
  - Ladd, R. T., 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 424)
  - Lamar, Howard, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 425)
  - Lamb, W. K., 1931 (Box 5, Folder 426)
  - Lambert, J. D., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - Lanahan, Caroline M., undated (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - Landall, L. W., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - Laning, Paul F., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - Larson, Laurence M., 1917 (Box 5, Folder 431)
  - Lascelles, Francis, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 432)
  - Laslett, Peter, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 433)
  - Lathrope, R. G., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 434)
  - Laverick, W., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 435)
  - Lawson, L. A., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - Lea, Kathleen, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 437)
  - Lee, Charles E., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 438)
  - Lee, Frank, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 439)
  - Leech, Hugh, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 440)
  - Leighton, Josephine, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 441)
  - Leland, Waldo G., 1911-1945 (Box 5, Folder 442)
  - Leyburn, Jim, 1944, undated (Box 5, Folder 443)
  - Lisle, Virginia S., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 444)
  - Lloyd, J. R., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 445)
  - Lobel, M. D., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 446)
  - Lohmann, Carl A., 1930-1951, undated (Box 5, Folder 447)
  - Lohmann, Helen (Mrs. C. A.), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 448)
  - Londonderry, Lady, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 449)
  - Lonhergan, Augustine, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 450)
  - Long, Olive M., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 451)
  - Longman, Mark, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 452)
  - Loos, Melvin, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 453)
  - Lopez, Robert S., undated (Box 5, Folder 454)
  - Lord, Barbara, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 455)
  - Lord, Bertha D., 1943-1950 (Box 5, Folder 456)
  - Loreaux, Ella, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - Lotham, Robert, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 458)
  - Loveday, A., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 459)
  - Loveman, Amy, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 460)
  - Lovett, Sidney, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 461)
  - Lowry, Howard, 1928-1944 (Box 5, Folder 462)
  - Lyman, David R., undated (Box 5, Folder 463)
  - Lyttelton, Norah, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - McAffe, Helen, 1929-1945, undated (Box 5, Folder 465)
  - McClenahan, Robert, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 466)
  - Macleod, Matthews, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 467)
  - McCleverty, Adelbert D., 1909 (Box 5, Folder 468)
  - MacCormack, J. R., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 469)
  - McDermott, William C., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 469A)
  - Macfarlane, B., undated (Box 5, Folder 470)
  - McFarlane, G. J., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 471)
  - McFee, William, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 472)
  - McKee, Irving, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 473)
  - McKee, John D., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 474)
  - McKechnie, H. M. M., 1931 (Box 5, Folder 475)
  - McKnight, Henrietta T., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 476)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 477)
  - McMillan, Emily, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 478)
  - Macmillan, Harold, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 479)
  - MacMillan, Kerr, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 480)
  - McMillan, Margaret, undated (Box 5, Folder 481)
  - Maitland, E., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 482)
  - Mallory, Herbert S., 1907-1908 (Box 5, Folder 483)
  - Malone, Dumas, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 484)
  - Maloney, Francis, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 485)
  - Mann, Albert R., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 486)
  - Manning, Frederick, 1930-1935 (Box 5, Folder 487)
  - Manning, Helen Taft, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 488)
  - Marshall, Horace and Son, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - Marshman, D. M., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 490)
  - Martin, H. F., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 491)
  - Martin, Ruth, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - Mathias, Barbara, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  - May, Alfred A., 1900-1908 (Box 5, Folder 494)
  - Meiggs, Russell, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 495)
  - Meikle, Henry W., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 496)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas, 1933-1965, undated (Box 5, Folder 497)
  - Merriman, O., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 498)
  - Merriman, Roger B., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 499)
  - Merz, Charles, 1939-1943 (Box 5, Folder 500)
  - Metzger, Charles H., 1927-1929 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  - Middleton, L. W., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  - Miller, David, 1927-1929 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - Miller, Hunter, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 504)
  - Miller, John C., 1900-1902 (Box 5, Folder 505)
  - Miller, Perry, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 506)
  - Milne, Taylor, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 507)
  - Mims, Stewart L., 1912-1928 (Box 5, Folder 508)
  - Mitchell, Kendall, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 509)
  - Mitchell, Sidney K., 1929-1931 (Box 5, Folder 510)
  - Mitchell, William, 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 511)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1939-1949 (Box 6, Folder 512)
  - Moir, Thomas L., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 513)
  - Monaghan, Frank, 1928-1930 (Box 6, Folder 514)
  - Monger, Arthur P., 1912-1914 (Box 6, Folder 515)
  - Moore, J. Allen, 1898-1902 (Box 6, Folder 516)
  - Moore, R. H., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 517)
  - Morand, Ruth, 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 518)
  - Morehouse, Andy, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 519)
  - Morgan, Edmund, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 520)
  - Morgan, William Thomas, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 521)
  - Morison, Samuel E., 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 522)
  - Morrill, H., undated (Box 6, Folder 523)
  - Morris, E. P., undated (Box 6, Folder 524)
  - Morrison, H. P., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 525)
  - Morrow, Glenn R., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 526)
  - Mowat, R. B., 1930 (Box 6, Folder 527)
  - Mullins, E. L. C., 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 528)
  - Mumford, W. B., undated (Box 6, Folder 529)
  - Munro, Dana C., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 530)
  - Murdock, Kenneth B., 1939 (Box 6, Folder 531)
  - Murphey, Thomas D., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 532)
  - Murray, John, 1934-1937 (Box 6, Folder 533)
  - Namier, Louis B., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 534)
  - Nangle, Benjamin Christie, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 535)
  - Neale, J. Ernest and Elfreda, 1925-1967 (Box 6, Folder 536)
  - Neilson, Nellie, undated (Box 6, Folder 537)
  - Neilson, W. A., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 538)
  - Nelson, Ernest W., 1928-1935 (Box 6, Folder 539)
  - Nesbitt, Naudie Linn, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 540)
  - Nettleton, George H., undated (Box 6, Folder 541)
  - Nevins, Allan, 1928-1939 (Box 6, Folder 542)
  - Newhall, Richard A., 1911 (Box 6, Folder 543)
  - Newton, Percival, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 544)
  - Nicholas, Herbert and Eveline, 1937-1966 (Box 6, Folder 545)
  - Nicholson, Hedley Hope, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 546)
  - Nicholson, Marjorie, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 547)
  - Nicoll, Allardyce, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 548)
  - Nordell, Philip G., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 549)
  - Northrop, Cyrus, 1909-1910 (Box 6, Folder 550)
  - Northrop, George N. and Catharine P., 1913-1922, undated (Box 6, Folder 551)
  - Norton, Walter C. N., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 552)
  - Notestein, Ada, 1940-1951, undated (Box 6, Folder 553)
  - Notestein, Frank, 1928-1965 (Box 6, Folder 554)
  - Notestein, James O., 1906-1919 (Box 6, Folder 555)
  - Notestein, Lucy Lilian, 1906-1967, undated (Box 6, Folder 556)
  - Notestein, Margaret (mother), 1906-1907, undated (Box 6, Folder 557)
  - Notestein, Robert, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 558)
  - Notestein, Margaret Wallace, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 559)
  - Notestein, Wallace, 1901-1967, undated (Box 6, Folder 560)
  - Notestein, W. L., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 561)
  - Nottingham, Betty, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 562)
  - Nowlin, Nadine, 1909, undated (Box 6, Folder 563)
  - Noyes, William D., 1 899-1 947 (Box 6, Folder 564)
  - Nugent, Mary V., 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 565)
  - O'Conor, May, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 566)
  - Ogg, David, 1935-1947, undated (Box 6, Folder 567)
  - Oldman, C. B., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 568)
  - Olmstead, Ashley W., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 569)
  - Oppenheimer, Michael, 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 570)
  - Oppenheimer, Robert, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 571)
  - Ormerod, Barbara S., undated (Box 6, Folder 572)
  - Osgood, Herbert L., 1912 (Box 6, Folder 573)
  - Ostrander, H. J., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 574)
  - Otto, Hildur (Mrs. Henry C.), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 575)
  - Overall, Nadine Webb, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 576)
  - Oviatt, Edwin, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 577)
  - Owen, Louise and David, 1938-1968 (Box 6, Folder 578)
  - Packard, Laurence B., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 579)
  - Paine, Anne, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 580)
  - Pares, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 581)
  - Parker, E. W., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 582)
  - Parker, Thomas, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 583)
  - Parmelee, E. W., 1912 (Box 6, Folder 584)
  - Parnis, A. E. L., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 585)
  - Parry, C. F., 1951-1955 (Box 6, Folder 586)
  - Peake, Alison, undated (Box 6, Folder 587)
  - Pearl, Valorie, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 588)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1938-1968 (Box 6, Folder 589)
  - Peel, Albert, 1942, undated (Box 6, Folder 590)
  - Pemberton, Betty, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 591)
  - Pemberton, Mira, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 592)
  - Pendleton, Elizabeth, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 593)
  - Perkins, Dexter, 1929-1939, undated (Box 6, Folder 594)
  - Perkins, Elliot, 1939-1940, undated (Box 6, Folder 595)
  - Phelps, Ruth Shepherd, 1911-1917, undated (Box 6, Folder 596)
  - Philipson, Stow, H. M., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 597)
  - Phillips, Ulrich B., 1929-1931 (Box 6, Folder 598)
  - Pickthorn, Kenneth, 1932-1936 (Box 6, Folder 599)
  - Pierson, George W., 1967-1968, undated (Box 6, Folder 600)
  - Pike, Joseph, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 601)
  - Piper, David, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 602)
  - Pittwin, Harry W., 1899 (Box 6, Folder 603)
  - Platter, Houston, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 604)
  - Plumb, J. H., 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 605)
  - Polk, Frank L., 1919 (Box 7, Folder 606)
  - Pollard, A. F., 1913-1935 (Box 7, Folder 607)
  - Pollard, Catherine, 1928-1931 (Box 7, Folder 608)
  - Pollock, James K., 1903-1965, undated (Box 7, Folder 609)
  - Poole, R. L., 1914 (Box 7, Folder 610)
  - Postan, M., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 611)
  - Potter, G. R., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 612)
  - Powicke, F. M., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 613)
  - Powicke, Susan, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 614)
  - Pratt, Robert A., 1945 (Box 7, Folder 615)
  - Prescott, F. C., 1927-1936, undated (Box 7, Folder 616)
  - Prescott, Orville, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 617)
  - Proffitt, Charles G., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 618)
  - Prothero, S. W., 1919 (Box 7, Folder 619)
  - Puehler, Alma, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 620)
  - Purcell, Richard, 1911-1913 (Box 7, Folder 621)
  - Pye, D. R., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 622)
  - Quinn, Vincent, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 623)
  - Raach, John, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 624)
  - Rabb, Theodore, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 625)
  - Ralph, Philip L., 1932-1947 (Box 7, Folder 626)
  - Randall, E. O., 1906 (Box 7, Folder 627)
  - Ratcliffe, S. K., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 628)
  - Rathbone, Maurice G., 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 629)
  - Read, Conyers, 1934-1940 (Box 7, Folder 630)
  - Read, Elizabeth, undated (Box 7, Folder 631)
  - Read, Kathleen, undated (Box 7, Folder 632)
  - Reddaway, T. F., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 633)
  - Reeder, Robert P., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 634)
  - Relf, Frances H., 1928-1952, undated (Box 7, Folder 635)
  - Renshaw, M. A., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 636)
  - Rickert, Edwin L., 1902 (Box 7, Folder 637)
  - Roberts, Llywelyn, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 638)
  - Robertson, Charles Grant, 1933-1937 (Box 7, Folder 639)
  - Robinson, Edgar E., 1916 (Box 7, Folder 640)
  - Robinson, Philip R., 1931-1940 (Box 7, Folder 641)
  - Bogardus, Ruth Elizabeth, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 642)
  - Rogers, Arthur, undated (Box 7, Folder 643)
  - Rostoutzeff, M., 1932-1933 (Box 7, Folder 644)
  - Rostow, Eugene V., undated (Box 7, Folder 645)
  - Rowse, A. L., 1939-1954, undated (Box 7, Folder 646)
  - Rudin, Harry R., 1937 (Box 7, Folder 647)
  - Russell, J. C., 1945 (Box 7, Folder 648)
  - Russell, S. A., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 649)
  - Russell, Warren E., 1911 (Box 7, Folder 650)
  - Rutland, Lord, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 651)
  - Ryall, G. W., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 652)
  - Sachse, William, 1936-1947 (Box 7, Folder 653)
  - Sale, Helen (Mrs. William M.), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 654)
  - Salisbury, Lord, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 655)
  - Sammons, Wheeler, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 656)
  - Sant, Fred G., 1907 (Box 7, Folder 657)
  - Sargent, Elizabeth Collier, undated (Box 7, Folder 658)
  - Satterthwaite, E. S., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 659)
  - Sayles, G. O., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 660)
  - Scammon, Julia and Richard E., 1932-1952 (Box 7, Folder 661)
  - Schaff, Harold H., 1932 (Box 7, Folder 662)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 663)
  - Schmitt, Bernadotte, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 664)
  - Schuyler, R. L., 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 665)
  - Scott, L. H., undated (Box 7, Folder 666)
  - Seaman, Owen, undated (Box 7, Folder 667)
  - Seney, Henry W., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 668)
  - Sergeantson, R. M., 1908-1912 (Box 7, Folder 669)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1927-1961, undated (Box 7, Folder 670)
  - Seymour, George Dudley, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 671)
  - Shapiro, A., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 672)
  - Shappell, J. M., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 673)
  - Sharp, Margaret, undated (Box 7, Folder 674)
  - Sharp, William T., undated (Box 7, Folder 675)
  - Shaw, William A., 1924-1926 (Box 7, Folder 676)
  - Sheppard, A. W., 1931 (Box 7, Folder 677)
  - Sheppard, J. J., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 678)
  - Sherman, Ruth, 1928, undated (Box 7, Folder 679)
  - Simmonds, H. M. J., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 680)
  - Simmons, L. N., 1923 (Box 7, Folder 681)
  - Simpson, Alan, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 682)
  - Simpson, Hartley N. D., 1928-1967 (Box 7, Folder 683)
  - Simpson, Hartley N. D., undated (Box 7, Folder 684)
  - Sitwell, George R., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 685)
  - Skeat, T. C., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 686)
  - Smith, Alice (Mrs. Cyril), 1946, undated (Box 8, Folder 687)
  - Smith, Bud and Maggie, undated (Box 8, Folder 688)
  - Smith, Shirley, W., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 689)
  - Smith, R. R., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 690)
  - Smyth, Charles, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 691)
  - Snortum, K. O., 1910 (Box 8, Folder 692)
  - Snow, Edith Huntington, undated (Box 8, Folder 693)
  - Soull, L. P., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 694)
  - Southworth, Hamilton, undated (Box 8, Folder 695)
  - Sparrow, John, 1932-1937 (Box 8, Folder 696)
  - Squire, Marjorie, undated (Box 8, Folder 697)
  - Stahl, Margaret, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 698)
  - Stanley, Sidney C., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 699)
  - Stearns, Malcolm, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 700)
  - Steer, Francis W., 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 701)
  - Steever, Miller D., 1929 (Box 8, Folder 702)
  - Steinberg, Mrs. Michael, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 703)
  - Stephens, Michael, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 704)
  - Stevens, Emily, undated (Box 8, Folder 705)
  - Stillman, George S., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 706)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 707)
  - Stoll, Elmer E., 1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 708)
  - Stone, June E., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 709)
  - Strong, Eustace and Charlotte, 1941, undated (Box 8, Folder 710)
  - Strong, Frank, 1905-1908 (Box 8, Folder 711)
  - Stuart, Duane Reed, 1928-1933 (Box 8, Folder 712)
  - Styles, Philip and Dorothy, 1935-1968, undated (Box 8, Folder 713)
  - Sumner, Humphrey and Beatrix, 1948, 1950, undated (Box 8, Folder 714)
  - Sutherland, Lucy, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 715)
  - Swan, Mabel, undated (Box 8, Folder 716)
  - Swanson, Neil H., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 717)
  - Sweet, Gordon, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 718)
  - Swift, F. H., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 719)
  - Tawney, R. H., 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 720)
  - Taylor, A. M., undated (Box 8, Folder 721)
  - Taylor, Shelagh, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 722)
  - Tener, Alexander C., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 723)
  - Thilly, Gertrude, undated (Box 8, Folder 724)